[
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (4x + 7) + (7x + 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "10x + 11",
        "12x + 11",
        "11x + 11",
        "11x + 12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (4x + 3) + (3x + 4)?",
      "correctAnswer": "7x + 7",
      "options": [
        "6x + 7",
        "7x + 8",
        "8x + 7",
        "7x + 7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 3) + (3x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "8x + 8",
      "options": [
        "9x + 8",
        "8x + 9",
        "7x + 8",
        "8x + 8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 10) + (10x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "20x + 20",
      "options": [
        "20x + 21",
        "21x + 20",
        "20x + 20",
        "19x + 20"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (7x + 10) + (10x + 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "17x + 17",
      "options": [
        "17x + 17",
        "18x + 17",
        "16x + 17",
        "17x + 18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (7x + 7) + (7x + 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "14x + 14",
      "options": [
        "13x + 14",
        "14x + 14",
        "14x + 15",
        "15x + 14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 5) + (5x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "10x + 10",
        "11x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "9x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 2) + (2x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "5x + 5",
      "options": [
        "5x + 5",
        "5x + 6",
        "4x + 5",
        "6x + 5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (1x + 5) + (5x + 1)?",
      "correctAnswer": "6x + 6",
      "options": [
        "6x + 6",
        "6x + 7",
        "7x + 6",
        "5x + 6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 2) + (2x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "11x + 10",
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 10",
        "10x + 11"
      ]
    }
]